* * *

The Stitcher app and web listening are no longer available. Check out our [Farewell FAQs](https://stitcher.helpshift.com/hc/en/1-stitcher/section/151-stitcher-updates/) for more details.

Stitcher Privacy Policy
=======================

### Last updated: June 30th, 2023

The Stitcher apps and web listening will be shutting down on Aug 29. Check out our [Farewell FAQs](https://stitcher.helpshift.com/hc/en/1-stitcher/section/151-stitcher-farewell-1687885657/) for more details.

For Your California Consumer Privacy Act Rights, please read “Section 10. Additional Privacy Rights under U.S. State Laws” below.

Stitcher Media LLC (“**Stitcher**”) is a subsidiary of Sirius XM Radio Inc. (“**Sirius XM**”) and operates a variety of brands, products and services related to the distribution and monetization of podcasts through websites, applications, tools, and platforms (collectively, the “**Stitcher Service**” or the “**Service**”). Stitcher operates an account-based podcast delivery service direct to listener through the Stitcher website, mobile application or online player. Additional products and brands operated by Stitcher include, but are not limited to, Midroll, Earwolf, and Podswag, as well as certain original podcast brands produced by or for Stitcher. We may refer to Stitcher as "**we**", "**us**", or "**our**". We may refer to you as "**listener**", "**you**", or "**your**". The purpose of the Stitcher Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) is to inform you about the personal information Stitcher collects, how we use and share personal information, and the ways in which you can control how we use and share personal information. The current version of this Policy may be found at [www.stitcher.com/privacy](https://www.stitcher.com/privacy). Sirius XM’s privacy policy may be found at [www.siriusxm.com/privacy-policy](https://www.siriusxm.com/privacy-policy).

BY INSTALLING, USING, REGISTERING FOR OR OTHERWISE ACCESSING THE SERVICE, YOU AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND CONSENT TO THE PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY. **IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT INSTALL, USE, REGISTER TO OR OTHERWISE ACCESS THE SERVICE.**

Stitcher collects personal information about our users in various ways, including by your voluntary submissions and participation in and access to the Service, as well as through tracking technologies such as cookies, tags or similar technologies for mobile apps. The information Stitcher collects may be used in a variety of ways, including for internal review, to improve the Service, to notify you about updates to the Service, or promotions that you may be interested in, to fulfill and provide Service as requested by you, and to deliver and review the effectiveness of advertising, including contextual (interest-based) or behavioral advertising.

1\. Our Cookie Policy
---------------------

**Our use of Cookies**: Stitcher.com uses technology that is commonly known as "cookies." A cookie is a file written to your hard drive when you visit any Stitcher website. Some cookies remain on your drive and provides us or a third party with information assigned to an identifier for you. Cookies have different functions, including those that are necessary for the site to work; those that facilitate the functionality of the site, such as remembering what you listened to on a previous visit, give us information on the performance of the site, e.g., the time it takes to load, and other information we use to improve our product and your experience; and those used to measure, deliver and allow reporting for advertisements that we place for our Service or that we offer to third party advertisers using our Service. We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You may indicate your preference to reject some cookies through a banner on the website. Indicating you “reject” cookies in the banner will block most but not all cookies; for example, you cannot block cookies necessary for the site to deliver service. In addition, some cookies in forms, encoded in the pages of the website or embedded in third party advertising creative cannot be seen by the banner’s blocking mechanism and will not be blocked.

You may be able to manage cookies on your device by following the directions provided in your browser's settings. Most browsers allow you to:

* see what cookies you've got and delete them on an individual basis
    
* block third party cookies
    
* block cookies from particular sites
    
* block all cookies from being set
    
* delete all cookies when you close your browser

If you choose to delete cookies, you should be aware that any preferences for the website on that device will be lost.

We use cookies to monitor site performance, to remember you when you return to the site, to personalize your site experience based on your interests or what you listened to before. We use the identifier in a cookie to help us manage and report on your interaction with the Stitcher Service. Through cookies, we are able to collect information that we use to improve the Service, keep count of return visits to our website or our advertisers' or other third parties’ websites, collect and report on aggregate statistical information, authenticate your login credentials, or manage multiple instances of the Service in a single browser. We may also collect other data such as the page or site that referred you to the Stitcher Service, the date and time you visited the Service, and the IP address from which the website is accessed. If you do not accept these first-party cookies, you may still use the Service, but your experience with the Service will be limited.

**Advertisers' and other third parties' use of cookies**: Advertisers and other third-party advertising entities that deliver ads to you through the Service’s online applications may place or recognize a unique cookie on your hard drive. Advertising entities may use third-party cookies in order to count your exposure to or gauge your interaction with an ad. They may also use third-party cookies to provide you with interest-based advertising. Third-party cookies are not covered by this Policy. We do not have access to or control over cookies placed by advertisers and other third parties.

**Beacons, tags or other tracking pixels**: Stitcher, its service providers, and in some instances, advertising companies may also employ other technologies, known as "beacons", “tag” or "tracking pixels" (each, a "**Beacon**"). A Beacon is a one-pixel-by-one-pixel clear image that is embedded in HTML content, and is about the size of a period at the end of a sentence. The Beacon transmits information to a server, such as a numeric count, unique identifier, or IP address. Stitcher and third parties that we contract with use Beacons to help us better manage content on the Stitcher Service and in our communications with you, for example, to let us know which emails recipients have opened, or to count the number of unique visitors to a particular webpage. You cannot turn off beacons in emails.

**Embedded Scripts.** An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Stitcher, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily used by our server or a third party service provider or business partner while you browse or interact with the Stitcher and is deactivated or deleted when you disconnect from the Stitcher.

**HTML5 and Flash Local Storage**: Stitcher or its advertising and technology providers may, in some instances, use HTML5 and/or Flash Local Storage (collectively, "**Local Storage**") to enhance your listening and advertising experiences on the Service. Each browser implements HTML5 Local Storage differently and provides tools for managing content stored within local storage. You can review your browser's privacy settings to manage the content stored within HTML5 Local Storage. Similarly, for more information on how to manage content stored with Local Storage, please review this document provided by [Adobe](https://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html).

**Data Collected Through Mobile Devices.** We use embedded scripts and the tools provided in Software Development Kits (“SDKs”) to collect information through mobile devices such as the hardware model, operating system and version, identification numbers assigned to your mobile device, such as the ID for Advertising (IDFA) on Apple devices, and the Advertising ID on Android devices, mobile network information, and website usage behavior. SDKs are software packages that contain a set of tools that can be used to help build applications and implement new features in existing apps including those that collect information from your device.

2\. Information We Receive from or Collect about You
----------------------------------------------------

Stitcher collects personal information directly from you, automatically through the device you use to access the Services or websites such as Podswag, and from third parties about you.

Category of PI collected - Account Registration Data (Contact Information)

Identifiers and Contact Information (such as name, email address, account name or alias, username, password, IP address, account ID, other device and other technological identifiers) When you sign up for Stitcher, you provide us with your email address as well as a password for your account.

Categories of Third Parties/Service Providers the Data is Disclosed To

* Analytics Providers
    
* Data Centers
    
* Cloud Computing Providers
    
* IT Services
    
* Technology Maintenance Providers
    
* Security Vendors
    
* Customer Service Providers
    
* Payment processors
    
* Accounting and Financial service providers,
    
* Analytics insights provider
    
* Advertising vendor
    
* Direct marketing vendors
    
* Affiliated brands and entities
    
* Law Enforcement and Government agencies,
    
* Third parties in connection with court or other legal actions,
    
* Third parties in the course of a Business Transition,
    
* Third party sponsors, content creators, or other business relationships

Business or Commercial Purposes for which PI is Collected

Provide You Services

* Process transactions and orders
    
* Facilitate access to Stitcher services
    
* Create and manage your account on Stitcher
    
* Identify and recognize you across services and devices
    
* Send service and account related communications
    
* Respond to your inquiries
    
* Provide customer service
    
* Send you information that you requested or agreed to receive such as newsletters
    
* Facilitate your participation in activities you sign up for such as sweepstakes, contests, research

Internal Business Purposes

* To improve our services
    
* Develop new products and services
    
* Market research, auditing and publication
    
* Understand how you use our services, including analyzing trends and usage patterns
    
* Analyze the effectiveness of our marketing efforts

Advertising

* Send you special deals, offers
    
* Invites to events, and similar information from us or third parties)
    
* Provide you with information about content, products, offers, promotions, special deals or services offered by us or of third parties that we think may interest you

Personalization

* To tailor content, including advertising and listening recommendations, to you on the Stitcher
    
* To monitor and control the ad delivery, performance and frequency

Administrative

* Investigate and prevent fraud and other illegal activities
    
* Detect and troubleshoot technical issues

Legal

* To resolve disputes
    
* Enforce our agreements and policies
    
* Protect our or others’ rights/assets
    
* Comply with our contractual obligations
    
* Cooperate in governmental or other legal inquiries
    
* Fulfill regulatory reporting obligations; in connection with a business transition

Other Purposes as Disclosed at the time of collection/ with your consent

Third Parties to whom the Data is Sold/Shared for Targeted Advertising

* Third-Party Advertising and Analytics Partners
    
* Social Media and Other Third-Party Platforms
    
* Third-Party Business Partners

Category of PI collected - Payment Information

When you choose to subscribe to the Stitcher Premium Service, purchase the Stitcher Premium Service as a gift, or purchase merchandise on Podswag, you provide payment method information and certain other information expressly for authentication. We use third party payment processing service providers, such as Stripe and Paypal, to process payments for the Stitcher Service. You may be providing the Payment Information directly to the third party service provider acting on our behalf.

Categories of Third Parties/Service Providers the Data is Disclosed To

* Customer Service Providers
    
* Fraud monitoring and prevention
    
* Information security service providers
    
* Logistics providers
    
* Payment and transaction processors
    
* Affiliated companies or their subsidiaries

Business or Commercial Purposes for which PI is Collected

* Provide You Services
    
* Process transactions and orders
    
* Refunds
    
* Verify your eligibility to and facilitate your access to the Stitcher Service

Administrative

* To fight chargebacks ,
    
* To conduct sales audits
    
* Investigate and prevent fraud and other illegal activities

Legal

* To resolve disputes
    
* Enforce our agreements and policies
    
* Protect our or others’ rights/assets
    
* Comply with our contractual obligations
    
* Cooperate in governmental or other legal inquiries
    
* Fulfill regulatory reporting obligations

Third Parties to whom the Data is Sold/Shared for Targeted Advertising

This category of data is not sold or shared for targeted advertising.

#### Category of PI collected - Transaction Information or Commercial Information

Commercial information such as products or services purchased, obtained, or considered from Stitcher, or other purchasing or consuming histories.

Categories of Third Parties/Service Providers the Data is Disclosed To

* Technology Service Providers
    
* Customer Service Providers
    
* Order Fulfillment Service Providers
    
* Analytics insights provider
    
* Advertising vendor
    
* Direct marketing vendor
    
* Affiliated brands and entities
    
* Contextual online experience provider
    
* Data center
    
* Fraud monitoring and prevention
    
* Human resources service provider
    
* Information security service provider
    
* Social media platform

Business or Commercial Purposes for which PI is Collected

Provide You Services

* Facilitate access to Stitcher services
    
* Create and manage your account on Stitcher
    
* Send service and account related communications
    
* Provide customer service
    
* Verify your eligibility to and facilitate your access to the Stitcher Service

Internal Business Purposes

* Provide and improve our services
    
* Market research
    
* Auditing and publication
    
* Understand how you use our services
    
* Including analyzing trends and usage patterns

Advertising

* To send you special deals
    
* Offers, invites to events, and similar information from us or third parties

Personalization

* To tailor content, including advertising and listening recommendations
    
* To you on the Stitcher and on other websites and services

Administrative

* Investigate and prevent fraud and other illegal activities; detect and troubleshoot technical issues

Legal

* To resolve disputes
    
* Enforce our agreements and policies
    
* Protect our or others’ rights/assets; comply with our contractual obligations
    
* Cooperate in governmental or other legal inquiries
    
* Fulfill regulatory reporting obligations; in connection with a business transition

Third Parties to whom the Data is Sold/Shared for Targeted Advertising

* Third-Party Advertising and Analytics Partners
    
* Social Media and Other Third-Party Platforms
    
* Third-Party Business Partners

Category of PI collected - Listening Activity and Personal Preferences or Inferences drawn from information we collect

When you use the Service, we collect information about your usage including your listening activity, which may include the number and title of shows you have listened to, the content you prefer, the episodes you skip, and when and how long you listen. This may include your favorite shows.

Categories of Third Parties/Service Providers the Data is Disclosed To

* Technology Service Providers
    
* Third-Party Business Partners
    
* Third-Party Advertising and Analytics Partners
    
* Social Media and Other
    
* Analytics insights service provider
    
* Direct marketing (e.g., email, text, telephone, postal) vendor
    
* Affiliated brands and entities
    
* Contextual online experience provider

Business or Commercial Purposes for which PI is Collected

Internal Business Purposes

* Provide and improve our services; develop new products and services
    
* Market research
    
* Auditing and publication
    
* Understand how you use our services, including analyzing trends and usage patterns)
    
* To enhance your experience on the Service and to tailor content recommendations

Advertising

* To send you special deals, offers, invites to events, and similar information from us or third parties

Personalization

* To tailor content, including advertising and listening recommendations, to you on the Stitcher and on other websites and services

Legal

* To resolve disputes
    
* Enforce our agreements and policies; protect our or others’ rights/assets; comply with our contractual obligations
    
* Cooperate in governmental or other legal inquiries
    
* Fulfill regulatory reporting obligations; in connection with a business transition

Third Parties to whom the Data is Sold/Shared for Targeted Advertising

* Third-Party Advertising and Analytics Partners
    
* Social Media and Other Third-Party Platform
    
* Third-Party Business Partners

Category of PI collected - Technical Information or Internet or other activity information

As an internet-enabled service, Stitcher may collect certain technical information through the use of log files and servers. Web and application servers create log files automatically as part of their setup and configuration. Information in a log file may include IP address, operating systems and browser type, Internet service provider, date/time stamps, file requested, and other usage information and statistics.

Categories of Third Parties/Service Providers the Data is Disclosed To

* Technology Service Providers
    
* Customer Service Providers
    
* Information security service provider
    
* Fraud monitoring and prevention
    
* Affiliated companies.
    
* Third party advertising and analytics companies
    
* Other third parties (including government agencies)

Business or Commercial Purposes for which PI is Collected

Internal Business Purposes

* Research, understand how you use our services, including analyzing trends and usage patterns
    
* Facilitate your access to the Stitcher Service
    
* To enhance your experience on the Service and to tailor content recommendations

Improvement

* To improve our product and services
    
* Investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions and other illegal activities or activities that violate our policies
    
* Identify, diagnose and address technical issues

Personalization

* To tailor content, including advertising and listening recommendations, to you on the Stitcher and on other websites and services

Other Purposes as Disclosed at the time of collection/ with your consent

Third Parties to whom the Data is Sold/Shared for Targeted Advertising

* Third-Party Advertising and Analytics Partners
    
* Social Media and Other Third-Party Platform
    
* Third-Party Business Partners

#### Category of PI collected - Device ID/Interaction Information

This may include IP address, mobile device ID, Advertisement ID, MAC ID other unique ID, device information (device model, operating system version, date and time of access, mobile network information).

Categories of Third Parties/Service Providers the Data is Disclosed To

* Technology Service Providers
    
* Customer Service Providers
    
* Third-Party Business Partners
    
* Third-Party Advertising and Analytics Partners
    
* Social Media and Other Third-Party Platforms

Business or Commercial Purposes for which PI is Collected

Provide You Services

* Facilitate access to Stitcher services, create and manage your account on Stitcher
    
* Exercise territorial limits where required
    
* Internal Business Purposes
    
* Provide and improve our services; market research and auditing; understand how you use our services, including analyzing trends and usage patterns

Advertising

* To send you special deals, offers, invites to events, and similar information from us or third parties

Personalization

* To tailor content, including advertising and listening recommendations, based on your location on the Stitcher and on other websites and services

Administrative

* Investigate and prevent fraud and other illegal activities

Legal

* To resolve disputes; enforce our agreements and policies
    
* Protect our or others’ rights/assets; comply with our contractual obligations
    
* Cooperate in governmental or other legal inquiries
    
* Fulfill regulatory reporting obligations; in connection with a business transition

Other Purposes as Disclosed at the time of collection /with your consent

Third Parties to whom the Data is Sold/Shared for Targeted Advertising

* Third-Party Advertising and Analytics Partners
    
* Social Media and Other Third-Party Platforms
    
* Third-Party Business Partners

#### Category of PI collected - Location Information or Geolocation data

We will not collect your device-based location information unless you have permitted the Stitcher app to access location services on your device. You can control this access in your device’s system settings. We may approximate the region from which you are accessing the Service or our sites or other broad location from the IP address assigned to your device when you access the Service or site.

Categories of Third Parties/Service Providers the Data is Disclosed To

* Technology Service Providers
    
* Customer Service Providers
    
* Third-Party Business Partners
    
* Third-Party Advertising and Analytics Partners
    
* Social Media and Other Third-Party Platforms
    
* Contextual online experience provider
    
* Affiliated companies

Business or Commercial Purposes for which PI is Collected

Provide You Services

* Facilitate access to Stitcher services, create and manage your account on Stitcher
    
* Exercise territorial limits where required

Internal Business Purposes

* Provide and improve our services; market research and auditing; understand how you use our services, including analyzing trends and usage patterns

Advertising

* To send you special deals, offers, invites to events, and similar information from us or third parties

Personalization

* To tailor content, including advertising and listening recommendations, based on your location on the Stitcher and on other websites and services

Administrative

* Investigate and prevent fraud and other illegal activities

Legal

* To resolve disputes; enforce our agreements and policies
    
* Protect our or others’ rights/assets; comply with our contractual obligations
    
* Cooperate in governmental or other legal inquiries
    
* Fulfill regulatory reporting obligations; in connection with a business transition

Other Purposes as Disclosed at the time of collection /with your consent

Third Parties to whom the Data is Sold/Shared for Targeted Advertising

* Third-Party Advertising and Analytics Partners
    
* Social Media and Other Third-Party Platforms
    
* Third-Party Business Partners

#### Category of PI collected - Survey Responses

If you choose to participate in surveys or other research, we will collect personal information you choose to provide us and use it only for the purposes that are stated at the time the information is collected.

Categories of Third Parties/Service Providers the Data is Disclosed To

* Customer Service Providers

Business or Commercial Purposes for which PI is Collected

Internal Business Purposes

* Provide and improve our services; market research and auditing
    
* Understand how you use our services, including analyzing trends and usage patterns

Legal

* To resolve disputes; enforce our agreements and policies
    
* Protect our or others’ rights/assets; comply with our contractual obligations
    
* Cooperate in governmental or other legal inquiries; fulfill regulatory reporting obligations

Third Parties to whom the Data is Sold/Shared for Targeted Advertising

* Third-Party Business Partners

**Additional Details About our Data Practices:** We provide in this section additional details about the information practices listed in the chart above, where it would be helpful for your understanding of such practices.

**Friends and Family**: Certain features of the Stitcher Service, such as sharing content with a friend, may require you to provide personal information about the person with whom you want us to interact on your behalf. By providing another person's personal information to us, you confirm that you have the right to provide such information to us. If you choose to provide this information, we will store and use the information for purposes of providing the feature. For example, if you choose to purchase a Stitcher Premium subscription for a friend, we may ask for your friend's name and email address to provide the gift. We will only use this information for the specific reason for which it was provided or for security purposes, such as to prevent fraud. If you believe that one of your contacts has provided us with your personal information and you would like to request that it be removed from our database, please contact us at [privacy@stitcher.com](https://www.stitcher.com/privacy@stitcher.com).

**Legal and Security**: Finally, we may collect personal information pursuant to a legal, security or contractual requirement or to enforce our legal rights and obligations. In addition, we may use a variety of other technologies that collect similar device and device interaction information for security, fraud detection, and maintenance purposes.

We may also share your information in order to (i) protect or defend the legal rights or property of Stitcher, or the legal rights of third parties, employees, agents, and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements); (ii) protect the safety and security of Stitcher users or members of the public including acting in urgent circumstances; (iii) protect against fraud or to conduct risk management; or (iv) comply with the law, legal process, or legal and government requests.

**From Third Parties**: We may receive or collect information about you from third parties, and combine and store it on our servers with other information we may have already received or collected from you. These third parties include:

* Service providers that provide or make available advertising, features and functionality, and content on or through the Stitcher Service.
    
* Advertising entities such as advertisers and advertising agencies that collect and maintain information on their customers. These third parties may provide Stitcher with certain information about those customers for the purposes of serving advertisements and/or marketing offers to their customers on the Stitcher Service.
    
* Marketing companies and data providers that create, maintain, and distribute professional marketing lists or segments, or maintain and distribute other marketing, or similar data.
    
* Governmental or quasi-governmental agencies or organizations that provide or make available, to the public, census and demographic data.
    
* Third-party social media websites, applications, or services that you use to sign up for the Stitcher Service. In some cases, those websites, applications, or services may automatically provide us with information about you to facilitate personalization unless you use the controls available on those websites, applications, or services to opt-out of such sharing. We may host or facilitate interactions with social media or other third party platforms, like Facebook, YouTube, Instagram, Twitter, and Tik Tok which may include the ability to “like” or “share” content. You may also have the opportunity to log in through or otherwise connect your third party platform account. When you interact with these third party platforms through the Stitcher, we will receive information about you from the third party platform service and you will be choosing to share information about your interactions with Stitcher with that social media service. In addition, the third party platform service may set their own cookies and collect information about your use of the Stitcher, including your IP address or other device identifiers. These third party platforms may be able to collect certain information on your visits to the Stitcher regardless of whether or not you affirmatively interact with the feature and whether or not you are logged into (or have) an account with the third party platform. If you are logged out or do not have an account and visit a page with a social plug-in, your browser sends a more limited set of information. Like other sites, the third party platform will receive information about the webpage you are visiting, the date and time of your visit, and other browser-related information. They may use that information to help them improve their products or for other purposes set forth in their privacy policy. We may also receive information about you if other users of social media give us access to their profiles and you are one of their connections or "friends." The information collected and stored by the third party remains subject to the third party’s privacy practices, including, without limitation, whether the third party continues to share information with us, the types of information shared, and your choices with regard to what is visible to others on that third-party website or service. The third party may allow you to remove the application or feature, in which case we will no longer collect information about you through the application or feature but may retain the information previously collected. If you choose to post information to a third-party platform, that information may be public.

**Related Companies**: We may also receive information about you from our parent company, Sirius XM, and its affiliates, Pandora Media, LLC, AdsWizz Inc., Audio Ventures, Inc. d/b/a Simplecast, and their subsidiaries. For more information about the Sirius XM family of companies, please see [https://www.siriusxm.com/corporate](https://www.siriusxm.com/corporate).

We share personal information, including device information, we collect with our parent corporation, Sirius XM and its subsidiaries and affiliates to offer, provide, and improve services and products offered both individually and jointly with other Sirius XM companies.

**Podswag**: Podswag.com is Stitcher’s online store for the sale of merchandise on behalf of Stitcher, which may include merchandise offered by the permission of Stitcher’s parent company, SiriusXM, and its affiliates. Podswag.com is operated on behalf of Stitcher by the third party service provider, Shopify. Shopify’s privacy policy may be found at [www.shopify.com/legal/privacy](https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy).

**Jointly Offered Services:** If you elect a feature or service provided jointly by Stitcher and an affiliated company or a third party, we may share certain information about you with that affiliated company or the third party for account authentication and management, and to enable the Service or your account in conjunction with their platforms. For example, when you share information through integrated social networking platforms, such as Facebook, you agree to allow the Stitcher Service to communicate with the other service in order to set up your account or make those social features available for your use. Collection, use and disclosure of data by companies affiliated with Stitcher or by other third parties is covered by the respective privacy policy for each of those companies. You acknowledge and agree that you are responsible for your use of services originating or integrated with companies other than Stitcher, and that it is your responsibility to review their terms of use and privacy policies and the methods for managing privacy settings when using their services.

**Device Information:** Stitcher may share information we gather from devices you use to access the Service with its affiliates or with third-party vendors, service providers, manufacturers or distributors, or advertising companies for the following business and commercial purposes:

* to understand use of the Stitcher audience and its technological capabilities;
    
* to report to podcast publishers and creators on the use and performance of their content;
    
* to improve and extend our product offering, including in conjunction with our affiliates;
    
* to observe territorial limits for programming and advertising;
    
* to assist in marketing or advertising efforts, including but not limited to mobile listening capping, advertising frequency capping, and tracking advertising conversion events;
    
* to estimate the number of unique users;
    
* to provide security and detect fraud detection;
    
* to troubleshoot and debugging problems with the Stitcher Service; and
    
* to provide relevant advertisements, which may include cross-context behavioral advertising.

**Deidentified, Aggregated, or Anonymized Information:** Stitcher may share information that has been aggregated or anonymized and that can no longer be reasonably associated with you or your individual device. Such information may include such categories as demographic groups and their use of the Stitcher Service, location by region or country or type of operating system that access the service, or statistical information about interactions with the Stitcher Service. Such information is not considered personal information and is not addressed under this Policy. We may also de-identify information through the assignment of a pseudonym or other process; such pseudonymized information cannot be associated with you without being combined with additional information. We use and share de-identified information for business and commercial purposes for a variety of reasons, such as to analyze usage, improve the Stitcher Service and your listener experience, or to improve the serving and performance of advertisements and advertising campaigns. When de-identified information is stored, processed or shared in such a way that it shall not be combined with additional information to become re-identified, it is not personal information. Otherwise, we treat de-identified information as personal information, and this Policy governs accordingly our processing of such information.

**Information You Disclose in a Public Profile or in Public Forums:** You should be aware that any information you provide or post in any publicly accessible location such as a page, blog, or social media platform may be read, collected, and used by others who access it. Stitcher has no responsibility for any personal information you display in a public forum.

**Successor in Interest:** We may share your personal information with a successor in interest to Stitcher in the event of a corporate reorganization, merger or sale of all or substantially all of our assets.

3\. Third Party Advertising, Measurement, and Analytics and Your Choices
------------------------------------------------------------------------

**Opting Out of Interest-based Advertising:** In our effort to provide you with advertisements that may interest you, Stitcher, its affiliates and third-party advertising entities may use data in the manner disclosed in this Privacy Policy to provide you with relevant ads. To learn about how the online advertising industry uses information it collects to provide you with relevant ads, and to control whether you want to receive those relevant ads from third-party advertisers, please review the information at: [Understanding Online Advertising (About Our Ads)](https://www.aboutads.info/consumers). We do not control the privacy practices of third-party advertising companies.

If you are using an iOS-based device and do not want to receive tailored in-application advertisements that relate to your interests, you may be able to limit these advertisements by enabling "Limit Ad Tracking" on your iOS Device following these [instructions from Apple](https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT202074). If you are using an Android-based device and you do not wish to receive tailored in-application advertisements, you can visit [Google's Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/) page from a browser on your Android-based device and make your choices there.

Please note that your opt-out choices are browser and device specific; if you disable your cookies, upgrade your browser after opting out or if you use multiple different Devices, please opt-out on each device and each browser separately. Also, opting out through these mechanisms does not opt you out of being served advertising and you will continue to receive generic ads while online.

Some countries’ and certain U.S. states’ laws provide consumers with the right to limit or opt-out of the use of personal information for behavioral advertising across applications and across time. Even when you opt-out if applicable in your jurisdiction, your personal information may still be used to confirm ad delivery, measure campaign performance, cap the frequency with which the same ad is shown to you, or perform other measurement and reporting functions to the extent allowed by law.

4\. Do Not Track Signal and Global Privacy Control
--------------------------------------------------

Do Not Track (“DNT”) signals offered by some web browsers are settings that request that a web application disable its tracking of an individual user. When you choose to turn on the DNT setting in your browser, your browser sends a special signal to websites, analytics companies, ad networks, plug in providers, and/or other web services you encounter while browsing to stop tracking your activity. You can learn more about and set up Do Not Track [here](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/).

**Global Privacy Controls:** Global Privacy Control (“GPC”) is a technical specification in your browser settings that you can use to automatically inform websites of your privacy preferences with regard to third party online tracking. You can find out more about and set up GPC [here](https://globalprivacycontrol.org/#about).

Stitcher honors and responds to the GPC/DNT signal. Please note that when your browser broadcasts the GPC/DNT signal, we will limit the functionality of our website and prevent the website from transmitting your personal information to third parties. We will also treat this signal as a verified request to stop selling your personal information and stop processing your information for purposes of targeted advertising. However, the GPC/DNT signal does not fully identify you by name or email address. Therefore, we may not be able to honor this request for other interactions you may have or have had with Stitcher. You may also submit a Opt Out privacy request with your email, and other personal information for us to complete the opt-out process.

If you visit our website from a different computer or device, or clear cookies on your browser that store your preferences, you will need to return to this website to opt-out or rebroadcast the GPC/DNT signal.

5\. Managing Your Information
-----------------------------

We use the email address you provide to us to manage your account and for other purposes stated in this Policy. It is your responsibility to maintain the email address and keep it up to date. You have the option to opt-out of receiving promotional or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe link contained in the promotional, marketing, or other similar emails you receive. We will send you transaction confirmation emails and other Service-related announcements when it is necessary to do so. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

For instruction on how to change your information on or deactivate your account, please visit the [Stitcher FAQs](https://www.stitcher.com/faqs).

6\. Security and Content from Other Websites
--------------------------------------------

**Protection of Data:** We have implemented physical, technical and administrative security measures designed to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information we collect or receive from you. However, despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable.

**Data Integrity:** We use personal information in ways that are relevant and compatible with the purpose for which the information was collected or provided to us as disclosed in this Policy. We use technical and organizational measures to protect personal information we collect, process, and store from corruption or use in a manner inconsistent with our policies or the purpose for which we received it.

**Links to Other Websites:** The Stitcher Service and certain advertisements on the Service include links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Stitcher. If you submit personal information to any of those websites, the privacy statements and practices of those websites govern their use of your information. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any website you visit.

**Use of Framing Techniques:** Some of our third-party vendors may utilize framing techniques to serve content to and from webpages accessible through the Stitcher Service while preserving the look and feel of our website. If a third party utilizes framing techniques, you are providing your personal information to this third party and not to Stitcher.

7\. Our Policies Concerning Children
------------------------------------

Stitcher does not seek nor knowingly collect personal information from anyone under 13 years of age. In the event we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected information from children under the age of 13, we will take measures to remove such information from our servers.

8\. Retention
-------------

We retain your personal information as long as it is reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this Policy, considering the time period reasonably necessary to: provide the Service to you; exercise the choices and rights you have requested; comply with our contractual obligations; resolve disputes and enforce our legal rights and Terms of Use; and to comply with legal and regulatory requirements.

9\. Changes to our Privacy Policy
---------------------------------

We evaluate this Policy in light of new technologies, business practices, changes in law, and our listeners' needs, and may make changes to the Policy accordingly. To the extent allowed by applicable law, Stitcher reserves the right to change this Policy at any time. Stitcher will notify you of material changes by posting the changed or modified Privacy Policy on the Stitcher Service and at Stitcher.com and will otherwise notify you as required by applicable law. We may also provide notice to you in other ways, such as through contact information you have provided. Any changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Policy unless otherwise specified. Your continued use of any of the Stitcher Service, applications or websites after the effective date of the revised Policy will constitute your consent to those changes to the fullest extent allowed by applicable law. Stitcher will provide notice and obtain your consent (opt-in or opt-out) if required. However, you may need to consent to the revised Policy in order to maintain continued access and use to the Service or the applications.

10\. Additional Privacy Rights Under U.S. State Laws
----------------------------------------------------

Certain countries and U.S. states have implemented privacy laws specific to the jurisdiction. If you are a resident of such country or state, you may have additional privacy rights. Please see the following additional provisions, as required under the consumer privacy law of your jurisdiction.

**California Residents:** _Your rights under Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.83 (Shine the Light law)_: California residents may request certain information about categories of personal information shared by Stitcher with unaffiliated third parties for those parties’ own marketing purposes during the previous calendar year and the names of such parties. We share personal information with affiliated companies, Pandora Media, LLC, Sirius XM Radio Inc. and their subsidiaries and affiliates, who may use that information for any of the uses that Stitcher may use it. We do not share your personal information (as defined under this section) with third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless you specifically opt-in, or are offered the opportunity to opt-out at the time you provide personal information or request a service and elect not to opt-out.

_Your privacy rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (CCPA)_: CCPA provides for certain disclosures about your rights and the personal information we collect, sell, and disclose for business or commercial purposes. California residents have the right to request: (1) that we disclose to you what Personal Information we collect, use, disclose, share and sell, including the right to request that we provide to you the categories and specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected about you (“**Right to Know**”); (2) that we delete the Personal Information we collect about you, (“**Right to Delete**”); and (3) to opt-out from the sale of their Personal Information (“**Right to Opt-Out of Sale**”), all subject to the meanings and exceptions set forth in the CCPA.

If you are a California resident and would like to exercise one of your rights under the CCPA, please submit your request by sending an email to [privacy@stitcher.com](https://www.stitcher.com/privacy@stitcher.com). To exercise your Right to Opt-Out of Sale, you may also submit your request online [here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/613d75ce-3c5b-4623-bcef-a0d3694b4214/01f8fe2e-c0f0-481e-9615-f5bb1c5b4e45). In your request, you must provide enough information to allow us to verify that you are the person about whom we collected personal information, or their authorized representative. You must also describe your request with enough detail so that we can understand, evaluate, and respond to it. We can’t respond to your request if we can’t verify your identity. Making such a request does not require you to create an account with us, and we will only use the information you provide in a request to verify your identity and to maintain a record of your request.

Right to Know

California residents have the right to know the categories of information we have collected about you, which are described below, and to request access to the specific pieces of information, which we will deliver to you electronically, in a portable format where feasible. You can submit up to two access requests per 12 month period. In order to protect the privacy of our customers and in accordance with law, if you request access to the specific pieces of Personal Information, we will verify your identify to a reasonably high degree of certainty, which may require a signed declaration under penalty of perjury that you are the consumer whose Personal Information is the subject of the request.

Right to Delete

California residents have the right to request deletion of the Personal Information about you that we have collected from you.

Please note that as part of the verification process, once you submit a request to delete, we may follow up and require you to confirm that you want your information deleted. Please note that we are unable to delete information needed to:

* Continue to provide goods or services you’ve requested, complete a transaction or perform a contract;
    
* Help ensure security and integrity;
    
* Identify, repair, and debug errors that impair the Stitcher Services, websites or applications, systems, or other functionality;
    
* Comply with legal or reporting obligations, including to pursue or defend legal claims, exercise or enable others to exercise any rights provided by law, enforce or comply with contractual obligations, respond to valid requests for information, and comply with or enforce applicable laws and regulations;
    
* Enable other internal uses consistent with your expectations based on your relationship with us or the context in which you provided the information; or
    
* Enable or enforce any other exceptions provided by CCPA or CPRA.

Please note that a request for deletion of personal information does not cancel your Stitcher Premium subscription. We will retain such information as reasonably necessary to provide the service(s), manage contact preferences, and otherwise in accordance with the exceptions noted above. Please visit the [Stitcher FAQs](https://stitcher.helpshift.com/hc/en/1-stitcher/faq/885-how-to-cancel-stitcher-premium-1632938322/) for information on cancelling your subscription first before submitting the deletion request.

Right to Opt-Out of Sale

California residents have the right to opt-out of the sale of their Personal Information to a third party for cross-context behavioral advertising (i.e., targeted advertising), whether or not for monetary or other valuable consideration. We will act upon opt-out requests within fifteen (15) days of receipt.

Stitcher may disclose information to third parties for their own purposes, including to its affiliated companies, Sirius XM Radio Inc. and Pandora Media LLC. Stitcher also engages in online advertising practices (and certain analytics or similar activities). These activities may be considered a “sale” as defined in the CCPA. Stitcher.com uses cookies for purposes further detailed in Our Cookie Policy above. Cookies may be set by service providers or 3rd parties. Only cookies set by 3rd parties may be considered “sales” under the CCPA.

In addition, the Digital Advertising Alliance also offers tools for California consumers to send requests under the CCPA to opt out of the sale of personal information by some or all of the participating companies, which may allow you to further control the use of your data by third parties. For more information, visit [https://www.privacyrights.info/](https://www.privacyrights.info/).

Right to Nondiscrimination for the Exercise of a Consumer’s Privacy Rights

California consumers have the right to not receive discriminatory treatment for exercising CCPA rights. We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your CCPA rights.

Notice of Financial Incentive.

We collect personal information from you when you choose to sign up for an ad-supported Stitcher account and in connection with your use of the Stitcher Service. There is no subscription fee associated with your ad-supported Stitcher account. We use and share personal information we collect to sell, deliver, measure and report on advertising, which may include personalized advertising to the extent permitted by law. You may purchase, or receive as a value-added benefit to certain SiriusXM subscriptions, a Stitcher Premium subscription that allows you to receive some content without ads as well as other premium benefits. Maintaining your account and your subscription, if applicable, are completely up to you, and you can cancel your subscription at any time.

To the extent that the price difference for an ad-supported Stitcher account may be considered a financial incentive in order to permit Stitcher to collect and use consumer personal information to sell, deliver, measure and report on ads, the value is reasonably related to the overall value we receive from the personal information participants provide specific to the program minus the costs and expenses we incur in providing the program.

Verification

For your protection, you must provide sufficient information to verify your identity in order for us to fulfill a request to access or delete Personal Information. If you ask us to provide you with specific pieces of personal information, we will verify your identity to a reasonably high level of certainty. We may ask that you provide us with information, beyond your full name and email address in order to verify your identity and fulfill your request. If we are unable to verify that the individual submitting the request is the same individual about whom we have collected information (or someone authorized by that individual to act on their behalf), we will not be able to process the request. If we are unable to verify your identity as the requestor for your deletion request, but locate an account using the same information you submitted, we will process your deletion request as a “Do Not Sell” request on that account.

Authorized Agents

If you are an authorized representative submitting a request on behalf of a California resident, please submit the applicable request pursuant to these instructions. We will follow up to request a signed, written permission signed by the individual who is the subject of the request authorizing you to make the request on their behalf. The written permission must state your full legal name, the full legal name of the individual who is the subject of the request and needs to be clear about the permission granted. Alternatively, you may submit a copy of a power of attorney under Probate Code sections 4000-4465. In either case, please also indicate in your email the nature of your request. We will verify your identity and that of the consumer independently before we fulfill your request. We will ask the consumer to verify their identity directly with us, unless you as authorized agent are acting pursuant to a power of attorney under the California Probate Code. Please keep in mind that if we do not receive adequate proof that you are authorized to act on the consumer’s behalf, we may deny the request.

**Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, And Virginia Residents:** We set forth above the categories of personal data we process, the purpose for processing personal data, the categories of personal data shared, and the categories of third parties with whom personal data is shared. Residents of Virginia, Colorado, Connecticut, and Utah have certain privacy rights with respect to this data, as described below.

_Your Rights_

Access Your Information/Obtain Your Information/Data Portability (CO, CT, UT, VA Residents) You have the right to confirm whether we are processing your personal data and request to access such data, obtain a copy of the personal data previously provided by you to us and, to the extent feasible, in a readily usable format to allow data portability.

Delete Your Information (CO, CT, UT, VA Residents)

You have the Right to delete your personal data.

Correct Your Information (CO, CT, VA Residents)

You have the Right to correct the personal data we hold about you.

Opt-Out of Sale of Your Personal Data and Targeted Advertising (CO, CT, VA and UT residents)

You have the right to opt out of the sale of your data. Stitcher does not sell personal data to third parties for monetary compensation as defined by the Virginia and Utah laws and therefore does not offer this opt-out right to residents of Virginia or Utah.

Cookie Based Opt Outs for Sale and Targeted Advertising

Stitcher engages in online advertising practices (and certain analytics or similar activities), that in addition to being a “sale” under CO and CT law, are “targeted advertising” under VA, CO, CT and UT state laws. You may opt out of cookies set by 3rd parties that may be considered “sales” and “targeted advertising,” by launching the Cookie Settings from the footer of our web pages.

Stitcher does not process personal data for the purposes of profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects.

Right to Appeal (CO, CT, VA Residents) – If you are a resident of Colorado, Connecticut or Virginia, and you would like to appeal our decision relating to your request, you have the right to submit an appeal and can do so by clicking on the form [here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/613d75ce-3c5b-4623-bcef-a0d3694b4214/174f9a9c-be5c-4d07-b73a-3651f4dc3770).

Please include your full name, the basis for your appeal, and any additional information to consider. Depending on the applicable law, within forty five (45) to sixty (60) days of receipt of an appeal, Stitcher will inform you in writing of any action taken or not taken in response to your appeal. If the appeal is denied, you may contact

Virginia Attorney General (by email: mailoag@oag.state.va.us, or phone: 804-786-2071) to submit a complaint

Colorado Attorney General ( complaint submission link [https://complaints.coag.gov/s/contact-us](https://complaints.coag.gov/s/contact-us) or phone:(720) 508-6000, or email: [attorney.general@coag.gov](mailto:attorney.general@coag.gov))

Connecticut Attorney General ( complaint submission link [https://www.dir.ct.gov/ag/complaint/e-complaint.aspx?CheckJavaScript=1](https://www.dir.ct.gov/ag/complaint/e-complaint.aspx?CheckJavaScript=1) or phone: 860-808-5318 or email: [Attorney.General@ct.gov](mailto:Attorney.General@ct.gov))

Exercise Your Rights

If you are a Consumer residing in Colorado, Connecticut, Virginia or Utah (as defined in each state’s respective law) and would like to exercise your applicable rights as outlined above, please submit your request by sending an email to [privacy@stitcher.com](mailto:privacy@stitcher.com). You may also submit your request online [here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/613d75ce-3c5b-4623-bcef-a0d3694b4214/01f8fe2e-c0f0-481e-9615-f5bb1c5b4e45). In your request, you must provide enough information to allow us to verify that you are the person about whom we collected personal information, or their authorized representative. You must also describe your request with enough detail so that we can understand, evaluate, and respond to it. We can’t respond to your request if we can’t verify your identity. Making such a request does not require you to create an account with us, and we will only use the information you provide in a request to verify your identity and to maintain a record of your request.

**Nevada Residents:** If you are a resident of Nevada, you may apply limits to the sale of certain personal information to third parties for resale or licensing purposes, subject to applicable law. Stitcher does not sell your personal information for such use. You are entitled to register your preference for limits on such sales in the future by sending an email to [privacy@stitcher.com](mailto:privacy@stitcher.com), with the subject line, "Nevada Do Not Sell Request" along with your first and last name, zip code, and whether you are a former or current Stitcher listener. If you are a former or current Stitcher listener, in order to process your request, your email address must match the email address on your account.

11\. International Residents
----------------------------

**Basis for Processing Information:** Under privacy law in certain jurisdictions, businesses that control the processing of personal information must determine the lawful basis, for the processing, as defined by the applicable privacy law. Stitcher relies on the following lawful bases for our processing activities, respective to each activity: that you have consented to processing; that the processing is necessary for the performance of our contract with you; that we have a legal obligation; or that we have a legitimate interest in providing and improving the Services and managing our business operations.

**International Privacy Rights:** If you are a resident of a country other than the U.S., depending on your residence and subject to local law, you may have certain rights with respect to your personal information. These may include: the right to access, correct, and delete your personal information; the right to restrict or object to our use of your personal information; and the right to receive a portable copy of your personal information in a usable format. If you provide us with consent to use your personal information, you may withdraw that consent at any time, however, such withdrawal will not impact the lawfulness of our use of your personal information based on your consent up to that point. To make a request related to your personal information or otherwise exercise your rights, you may contact us using the contact information provided below. In order to fulfill your request, we may require additional information from you. We will respond to requests within the relevant time periods established by applicable law. We are committed to finding a fair and reasonable resolution to any request, concern, or complaint you bring to our attention. However, if you are unsatisfied with our response to your request, you may have the right to lodge a complaint with applicable governmental authorities, subject to local law.

**Data Transfers:** Our business operations are located primarily in the United States. If you choose to access the Service from outside of the U.S., personal information you provide to us or that we collect about you may be transferred to the U.S. and to other countries to be processed by us or our service providers in order to provide the Service to you or for such other purposes as set forth in this Policy. If you are not a resident of the U.S., by using the Service or by visiting the website, you consent and agree that we may collect, process, use, and store your personal information, as discussed in this Policy, outside your resident jurisdiction including in the U.S. Please be aware that U.S. law and the laws of other countries where we may store, and process personal information may offer different levels of protection for personal information than may be available in your country.

12\. Contact Us
---------------

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, or the privacy practices of Stitcher, contact us at [privacy@stitcher.com](mailto:privacy@stitcher.com), or write to us at Attn: Chief Privacy Officer - Stitcher, 8550 Freeport Parkway, Irving, Texas 75063 USA.

COMPANY

AFFILIATES

[Privacy Policy](https://www.stitcher.com/privacy) [Terms of Service](https://www.stitcher.com/terms) [Your Privacy Choices](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/613d75ce-3c5b-4623-bcef-a0d3694b4214/01f8fe2e-c0f0-481e-9615-f5bb1c5b4e45) Cookie Settings

© Stitcher 2024
